

♣ Profile

I study at ESPRIT specialized in Web Development. I am passionate about computer science, the web and new technologies. I like coding, developing web applications and learning new concepts. It's not easy but I don't give up. Every problem has its solution.

Employment History

Full Stack Developer at IPACT Consult, Canada

June 2021 — September 2021

As part of a professional internship, I developed an e-commerce web application named "Bakht'Art" that sells luxurious products related to fashion like Bathing Capes, Jebbas, Caftans...

Technical Environment: ReactJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, Git, HerokuApp.

Full Stack Developer | Quad Squad Group at ESPRIT, Ariana

February 2021 — May 2021

A project that serves to develop a webgen application named "GeniF'I" similar to wix and wordpress that allows companies to start their business and sell products or offer services by creating their own website by choosing one of the offered templates and customizing it in their own way.

Technical Environment: ReactJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, Git, HerokuApp.

Software Developer | Debug Entity Group at ESPRIT, Ariana

January 2020 — May 2020

A project that serves to develop a cross-platform application named Saviors: An associative donation platform that allows associations to add collections to which members can participate. It allows also suppliers to add their own products so that associations can buy for their own needs.

Technical Environment:

Symfony 3.4 Framework for Web Version as well as the REST APIs.

JavaFX for the Desktop Version.

Codename One for the Mobile Version.

Developer | Project Graduation at Nationa Office Post, Hedi Nouira Street

February 2019 — May 2019

As part of my end of study internship, I developed an e-commerce Web Application named "ePROD" that allows suppliers to sell their own products of any type so that customers can buy them.

Details

Le Bardo Tunisia +21620791462

sofien.ressaissi@esprit.tn

Date / Place of birth June 11 1995 Menzah 6, Ariana

Nationality Tunisian

Skills

HTML

IIIVIL

CSS

PHP

JavaScript

Java

JEE

React

Node.js

Angular

Symfony 3.4

Spring Boot

C# .NET

MySQL

MongoDB

Git

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Hobbies

Video Games Music

Technical Environment: Angular 7, Firebase.

Education

Web Development, ESPRIT, Ariana

September 2019 — Present

Computer engineer specializing in Web and Internet Technology

Computer Science & Multimedia, ISAMM, Manouba

September 2015 — May 2019

Fundamental license in computer science and multimedia.

Maths Baccalaureate, High School Bardo, Bardo

September 2013 — June 2014

Languages English

Eronch

French

Arabic